design-reuse.com 2019-12-02

# Design And Reuse, The System-On-Chip Design Resource - IP, Core, SoC

Design And Reuse appreciates your visiting its web sites :

**Scope**

Design And Reuse  (“D&R”, “we”, “us”, “our”) respects the privacy of users. We provide this notice in order to make sure that your expectations and our practices are aligned, and that you ( “User”) are aware of your choices with regard to D&R use and disclosure of the information you provide to D&R Sites. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit or use  [ **www.design-reuse.com**](http://www.design-reuse.com/), [**www.design-reuse-embedded.com**](http://www.design-reuse-embedded.com/), or  [ **www.design-reuse.cn**](http://www.design-reuse.cn/).

**Personal Information**

This Privacy Policy applies to information  you provide to us, including but not limited to, when : 

  * You create an account or a profile
  * Sign to receive D&R newsletters
  * When you  visit the Design And Reuse web sites (the “D&R Sites”), participating in our user community .
  * Also Information obtained through e-mail communications with the user,  related to the D&R Sites

Your use of these D&R Sites constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to any action we take with respect to your information in compliance with this Privacy Policy. We may amend or supplement  the terms of this Privacy Policy, so the Users are encouraged to review this page from time to time. Your continued use of these D&R Sites following the posting of changes to the Privacy Policy means that you accept the changes.

**Information We Collect and How We Collect It  **

We require you to provide certain information about yourself when you register on D&R Sites or subscribe to the newsletters.

The information we collect may include information from which you may be personally identified (“Personally Identifiable Information”), such as name, postal address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address, and certain business information such the place of employment and , occupation, job function, job title and buying information,. This includes also the information you provide when you make a request or otherwise contact us. We may collect the IP address of your computer. We also use automatic data collection technology to record other information that identifies your computer, browser type, operating system, and tracks your behavior on the only collect Personally Identifiable Information with your knowledge. 

**Cookies  **

Our websites may set cookies on your computer. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your computer by our web server and helps recall your use of this website. Cookies are safe for your device, uniquely generated and assigned to you. The primary purposes of cookies used by this website are to provide convenience, save you time and provide an enhanced experience. For example, we may use cookies to automate login, enable personalization or facilitate your movement through this website and measure site usage.  Should you not want to use the benefits offered by cookies, you can modify the use of  cookies on our websites. This will however prevent you from accessing some of our website's services as described earlier. If you do not disable the setting of cookies, you consent to your information being collected and used as set out in this Privacy Policy.

**Google analytics**

D&R Sites uses google analytics. For more information google analytics please see Google's help pages and privacy policy:  

**How We Use Your Information  **

We use Personally Identifiable Information collected on these D&R Sites for the following purposes: 

  * For registration purposes, to provide you with the access to D&R Sites and D&R services you have authorized
  * To provide you with the information you request
  * To deliver marketing communications, newsletters, as well as product news or notifications;
  * To respond to your inquiries and contact you about changes regarding the D&R Sites.
  * To generate and analyze statistics about your use of the D&R Sites
  * To communicate with you regarding information, features or offers that we believe will be of interest to you
  *  For any other purpose disclosed at the time the information is collected or to which you consent

Access to product descriptions provided by another company is contingent on your agreement that your contact details may be shared with the other company. We may share your Personal Information with third parties for the purpose of providing or improving the Services to you.

We may track your interest in that company's content or our own content over time and disclose your interest to that company - your email address and the other information you have provided to access to certain information - i.e products, white papers - will only be forwarded to our customers so that they can contact you about their offer and other relevant communications. It will not be used for any other purpose.

We may use the information you provide, to communicate with you on behalf of D&R. These communications may include e-mail newsletters that are relevant to these D&R Sites, as well as offers for other D&R services. All email newsletters will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of receiving future issues of the newsletter.

Your Personally Identifiable Information may be used also to send you e-mail on behalf of third parties. Each of these communications will include instructions for opting out of receiving future third party offers from us. You may also opt out of receiving third party offers from these D&R Sites at any time by sending us an email.

We also may use your Personally Identifiable Information to better understand our Users and to improve our D&R Sites. For example, we may use this information to determine what portions of the D&R Sites are most popular and the demographics of our Users generally.

**Children’s Privacy**

The Sites are not directed to, nor do we knowingly collect information from, anyone under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect, solicit or maintain Personally Identifiable Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. 

In case we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a someone  under 13 years of age, without verification of parental consent, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information from our database. Please contact us if you have any concerns.

**Our Disclosure of Your Information  **

We may disclose aggregated, anonymous statistics about many Users, and individual information that is not Personally Identifiable Information, without restriction as long as no individual is identifiable by the information disclosed, and otherwise will not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, except when stated otherwise (see hereabove).

**Data Retention**

The time periods for which we retain your Personal Information depend on the purposes for which we use it. We will keep your Personal Information for as long as you are a registered user of our services, for no longer than is required or permitted by law, or our data and records retention policy, reasonably necessary for internal reporting purposes, or to provide you with the information you might request. This period of retention is subject to D&R alteration.

**Security  **

We use administrative, organizational, technical and security reasonable safeguards to protect Personally Identifiable Information we collect on these  D&R Sites from unauthorized access, use, modification or disclosure. However, due to the design of the Internet and other factors outside of our control, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. 

**Links to Other Sites  **

These  D&R Sites contain content, services, advertising and other materials that link to Web sites operated by third parties. We have no control over those other sites, D&R Privacy Policy does not apply to them, and cannot be responsible for third-party websites and applications, including their content. We encourage you to refer to the privacy policies, if any, of those sites. 

**Right to Access and Change Information**

You may view and update information that you previously submitted to these D&R Sites by visiting [ **Profile Page**](https://www.design-reuse.com/users/change_settings.php)

**Right to Opting Out**

By providing us with your email address you consent to sending you D&R related notices,  messages or content, such as, but not limited to, D&R News Alerts, third-party newsletters, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out by emailing us.

**Right to Erasure/** Right To Be Forgotten

You may request deletion of your personal data (according to Article 15 GDPR) emailing us.

**Contact Information**

These D&R Sites are owned and operated by: Design And Reuse, S.A., 12 rue Ampere, 38 000 Grenoble, France. D&R welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions, please contact **[info@design-reuse.com](mailto:info@design-reuse.com) **
